What are you going to cook ?
Your favorite .
What , again ?
Well , this is the last one .
What , you mean my tomatoes ?
Can never have enough tins of tomatoes , eh ?
Instead ...
we 've five tons of chick peas .
Ooh .
That should last at least five year , eh ?
Fancy a glass of wine ?
Oh , yeah , that 'd be great .
Hey ;
You 're in luck .
Drinkable .
You all right , sweetheart ?
Yeah , I 'm fine .
Well , I 'm not fine . lt 's all fucked , isn 't it ?
Our children are safe , aren 't they ?
Totally , yeah .
Thank God we paid for that school trip .
Can you imagine if we hadn 't have done that ?
No , I can 't ... I can 't imagine .
I can 't imagine .
And I don 't want you to imagine it .
Listen , they 're far , far away ,
and they 're safe and sound .
Okay ?
Yeah .
Okay .
Don 't worry ...
Gorgeous .
Not interrupting , am I ?
No .
I found this in the cellar .
I 'd forgotten all about it .
I thought we could have them after dinner .
Yeah .
Mmm ! It smells wonderful .
And is that a bottle of wine , Don ?
Yes , indeed , Geoff .
Ah , thank you .
There 's chocolate for after .
Courtesy of your good lady wife .
What have we here ?
I get blackberries , vanilla , notes of autumn .
Karen ...
He 'll be hungry .
He 'll be hungry when he gets back .
He 'll want something to eat .
Here we go again .
Jacob , no .
Let me tell you something , sweetheart .
It 's been five days since your boyfriend run out on us .
If he 's breathing , it won 't be pasta he 's interested in .
Jacob !
It 'll be your fucking neck !
D-D-Don 't say that .
Out of orde , Jacob .
Why ? We all know it 's true .
The sooner she faces it , the better .
There are no survivors .
It 's just us in here and them out there .
- Sam ... ! - Quiet !
Let me in ! - lt 's a boy .
Wait , wait , wait , wait .
Don 't know who 's out there .
Please , let me in !
Don , it 's a kid !
Help ! Let me in !
Bloody hell .
Please , please let me in !
L 'm coming , I 'm coming ...
Let me in !
Please ! Help me !
Please !
Get in , get in .
Come on , get in ! Come on !
Are you all right ? Are you all right ?
Yeah .
Where have you come from ?
Sanford .
Sanford 's upriver a few miles .
How did you get here ?
They were chasing me .
Screaming .
I was scared . I ran .
I tried ... I tried other houses .
They were empty .
I came through the woods ...
Who were chasing you ?
My mum , my dad ...
They 're trying to kill me .
There 's others , too .
How many ?
Loads
Sam .
lt 's got my arm !
Help me !
Come on ! Get out of here !
Don !
Everybody go ! Go !
Geoff , I can 't see !
Hold onto my hand !
Get back !
Come back !
Oh , God .
Follow Jacob .
Keep going . Darling , there 's no time !
Come on ! Come on !
For God 's sake , go !
Fuck !
Where are you ! ?
Alice ! Alice , no ! Alice !
Geoff , come on ! Come on !
Geoff !
Give me your hand ! Give me your hand , Sally !
Geoff ! No ! No !
Help me !
Alice ! Alice !
Where are you ! ?
Just leave him .
I see him !
- Leave him ! - Let go !
Don ! Help us !
Don !
Help us !
$ 4 '
Jacob !
Go on !
â   Jacob ! ' Don !
Don !
Jacob .
Oh , shit . Oh , shit .
$ 4 '
Welcome to London .
Hey , Doyle , you having fun down there ?
You can kiss my ass .
This is the worst combat I ever saw .
Where 's the fucking combat ?
Yeah , I hear you .
Give me something to shoot .
Too easy .
PILOT ; Northeastern Med Center ,
20th floor , three windows in .
Fat guy jerking off in the toilet .
Oh , bug nuts - him again - I saw him yesterday .
I don 't see him .
Where is Fester Fuck Nut ?
Oh , your boyfriend ?
There he is , with his dick in his hand on the 20th floor .
Yeah , next to the fire exit , man .
Oh , shit .
I think he needs a jerk-off extender .
Hey , Doyle , you 're the expert in hand-to-hand combat .
- Man-to-man combat . - Shut up .
I think it might be your dad , Doyle .
- Ooh ! - You got him .
Shit .
Colonel Phillips here .
What is your current status ?
Good morning , Colonel .
Morning .
Colonel , I 'm watching the new arrivals disembark .
Yes , Major .
It 'll take all morning to process them .
Copy .
No one told me that we 're now admitting children .
just follow around to your right .
$ 4 '
Green and brown .
Interesting iris variation .
It 's usually hereditary .
Do one of your parents have the same ?
My mother , she did .
How old are you , Andy ?
Twelve .
I think that makes you the youngest person
in the entire country .
Well , your blood pressure is A-OK
and you 're negative on any serious diseases or afflictions .
I think you 're okay to come in .
Welcome back to Britain .
$ 4 '
We are headed
for the green zone , our area of security
and reconstruction , designated as District One .
District One is located on the Isle of Dogs .
Although the Isle of Dogs is completely safe ,
the surrounding area of London is not .
There are a large number of bodies still left to be cleared
from the original outbreak of infection .
Rats and wild dogs are prevalent , as is disease .
New arrivals are reminded , for their own safety ,
it is absolutely forbidden
to cross the river and leave the security zone .
You will be joining 15,000 civilians
who are already resident in District One .
As we approach your new home ,
you will notice a dramatically increased military presence .
The U.S. Army is responsible for your safety .
We will do everything we can do
to make your repatriation as easy as possible .
Inside District One , however ,
we believe you 'll be pleasantly surprised .
We have hot and cold running water ,
24-hour electricity , a medical center , a supermarket
and even a pub .
That sounds good .
We 're nearly home .
$ 4 '
- Dad ! - lt 's Dad !
- Dad ! - Dad ! Come on .
- I 'm excited . - Yeah .
You excited ?
Hey !
Oh !
I missed you so much .
You all right ? You all right ?
I never thought I 'd see you again , you know that ?
WOMAN ' . I am the chief medical officer .
I should have been notified before children were brought in .
We 've not even established the protocol for minors .
We have issues of disease and sanitation ,
not to mention , we don 't fully understand the virus yet .
We understand that it did not manage to go across species .
- Yes . - That it did not
manage to go airborne ,
and that the last infected human
died six months ago .
We weren 't here six months ago .
Major ...
What are you afraid of ?
What if it comes back ?
It won 't come back .
What if it does ?
If it comes back , we kill it .
Code Red .
Come on , guys .
What about this place , then , Andy ?
Eh ?
Yeah , it 's pretty good , Dad .
Look at the camera .
This way . That 's good .
There 's 25 floors .
We get the penthouse up there .
- Really ? - Really .
L.D. , sir .
- Thank you . - So what do you do here , Dad ?
What do I do ?
L 'm a section officer .
I keep the lights on ,
the water running , the heat running .
See , that 's what this says .
Triple A - â   access all areas.â   That 's me .
I basically run the place , you know ?
Well , you 're the caretaker , really , aren 't you ?
No , I run the place .
Wow !
Like it ?
It 's amazing .
What ? Even better than sunny Spain ?
You ought to have seen the refugee camps , Dad .
There were 20 of us in each tent and chemical toilets .
Oh .
- Everything smelled of piss . - Nice .
We 'll be moving to our new house soon ,
a couple of months , in fact .
A new house ?
Yeah .
Listen , I hope you guys understand , urn ...
we 're not going to be able to go back to our old house .
It 's outside the security zone ,
and anyway , I don 't think I 'd want to go back there ,
even if I could .
What happened , Dad - to Mum ?
Yeah .
Do you want to sit down and I 'll tell you all about it ?
Your mum and I were hiding in a house .
A wee cottage .
There was an old couple that ... owned it .
And they were there , too .
Three other people .
And we were , uh
just trying to stay alive , I suppose .
We were doing okay for a while .
And then we were attacked .
They came in through the kitchen window .
They were really fast , you know ?
Chased us .
Chased your mum .
And we were trapped .
Trapped in the bedroom .
Don !
I s ...
I seen them ...
biting ...
I couldn 't do anything .
I tried to go back .
She was already gone .
Was there nothing you could do ?
No , there was nothing I could do .
I managed to get away .
Just running , running and running .
I got to this military camp .
And you know the rest , you know , I 've been in quarantine ,
waiting for you guys to come back .
We 're just happy you 're still alive .
I 'm sorry .
$ 4 '
Doyle ...
Doyle , you bastard .
Boy , I 've never seen you get so white .
- Come on . - Oh , dude ...
Good morning .
Get the fuck out of here , man . I 'm having all good dreams .
Yeah ?
Sunday afternoon , clear blue skies .
I 'm laying in bed with my wife and ... now I 'm back
in this shit hole ...
I know , man .
Yeah , yeah .
I had that same dream about your wife .
Fucking with me .
Get on out of here , cowboy .
Yeah , all right .
Next time I 'm gonna shoot you , though .
All right , see you later , family man .
I told you I 'm gonna shoot you .
$ 4 '
What 's on the TV tonight ?
You okay ?
Bad dream ?
Hey ...
I get worried I 'm going to forget what she looks like .
You won 't forget .
I don 't even have a picture of her .
Promise ?
Yeah .
Andy , we agreed .
You heard what they said : it 's only dogs and rats out there .
We ' ll go home , We ' ll get What We Want and come back again .
We should have told Dad .
It 's fine . Trust me .
He won 't even know we 're gone .
$ 4 '
Where are you going ?
Base , come in .
Go .
We have two strays that just slipped out the north gate .
- Stray dogs ? - No , puppies .
Yeah !
- Yeah ! - Whoo !
- Yes ! - Yes !
Whoo !
Whoa ...
That 's what we need .
Yeah , if it had keys .
Wait here .
$ 4 '
Let 's go .
There you go .
$ 4 '
Tam !
Tam ?
Tam , are you there ?
Tammy ?
Tammy , this is stupid .
You 're not being funny .
$ 4 '
I knew it .
You 're hurting me !
No , don 't go ! No !
No !
Doyle ...
I got YOU ! " puppies .
No !
Get off me !
I apologize for these precautions .
It 's standard protocol when dealing with any survivors .
Though we haven 't had to do it for a while .
The last survivor we came across
was over two months ago .
Can you tell me anything about
how you managed to ... keep ... alive
while you were gone so long ?
Do you know of any other survivors ?
Okay .
Just going to take a blood sample .
It won 't hurt .
Have you come into direct contact
with the infected ?
Okay .
I want to see my children .
Of course . Of course .
Mr. Harris .
- Yeah . - We found your kids .
Oh , thank God , thank God . Thank you so much .
We found your wife , too .
Can they hear me ?
So what did you two think you were playing at ?
You said you saw her die .
What ?
You said you saw her die !
I didn 't say that .
You did , you said you saw her die , you did .
Baby , I didn 't use those words .
This is ...
I don 't know , I mean , it 's confusing , you know ?
It 's very hard for you to imagine , you know ?
It 's-it 's too hard to explain .
Well , try to explain it , Dad , try !
Try ? What do you want me to say ? I thought I saw Mom ...
die .
I wouldn 't have told you that ...
I was sure .
Guys , I 'm not sure what 's happening here ,
but it 's good .
Okay ? That 's the point .
Morn is alive .
I want to see her !
$ 4 '
There 's no question , sir .
She has the virus . She 's infected .
Why isn 't she showing any symptoms ?
I don 't know .
Speculate .
A genetic abnormality which acts
as some sort of natural immunity .
But the virus is still in her blood
and saliva , so ...
technically , she 's not immune .
She 's a carrier .
Are you saying she has the ability to infect others ?
Yes , sir .
Absolutely .
If this woman has natural immunity ,
she is incredibly valuable .
Her blood could contain the key to a vaccine , even a cure .
Alice ?
Hey , baby .
Oh , I 'm so sorry .
I was scared .
I shouldn 't have run away .
Please forgive me .
Please , sir , we need some time to study her .
We need to run some tests .
Run tests on her corpse , Major .
I love you , Don .
Yeah .
Oh , God , I love you , too .
$ 4 '
Don !
Help ...
Help me !
$ 4 '
Clear channels to control room .
Control room , this is General Stone .
All forces under my control
prepare to execute Code Red on my command .
- Affirmative . - Affirmative .
Break , break , break , all stations .
Sunray in 30 seconds .
We have an outbreak
of the infection in the medical center .
All units safeties off .
- Affirmative . - Affirmative .
Open air cap , transmission .
Prepare designated containment areas .
Affirmative .
Move civilians to containment areas .
All command personnel secure a bunker .
Confirm order to lock down .
Lock down confirmed .
Execute Code Red .
$ 4 '
Flynn , come in .
Flynn , did you hear that Code Red or am I losing my shit ?
Just about to ask you the same thing .
Ten hut !
Everything 's fine .
Don 't worry . I 'll be back in a moment .
It 's probably nothing .
Tam , it didn 't sound like nothing .
He said he 'd be back in a moment .
You Okay ?
Let 's go .
Come on .
Move , move , move ! Let 's go ! Let 's go !
Andy , keep hold of my hand !
Okay , come on , keep it going . Keep it moving .
Come on , people . Come on , people . Come on , now .
Don 't push . No pushing .
Sir , all civilians into the containment area .
- No , these kids are with me . - Sir ...
lt 's incredibly important that they are kept protected .
I need to get them out of here immediately .
Sir , no exceptions .
- It 's a Code Red . - I know what it is .
These kids are with me . My name is ...
- Andy ! - Scarlet !
' Andy !
- Andy ! - Andy , wait !
- Scarlet ! - just wait , Andy !
- We 're coming ! - Calm down . Calm down , now !
Move down , move down the room . Keep moving .
Go , go , go . Come on .
Keep moving . That 's it .
Hey , why are you shutting us inside here ?
For your own protection !
Well , just close the door ! You don 't need to lock it !
It 's for your own protection !
We 've got to find Andy .
It 's okay . We 'll find him .
Shut down civilian areas .
Sector One locked down .
Sector Eight locked down .
Sector Three locked down .
Switch to emergency lighting .
Use of non-lethal force authorized .
- All snipers in position . - Roger that .
Ground forces to med center . Ground force to med center .
- Sector One covered . - Where 's my spotter ?
Girls , stay calm .
Dad .
My dad ! My dad !
He 's in here !
No.1 . !
No !
Confirm : Only target infected .
Roger that . Only target infected .
Targeting right . I got two down .
Watch out for the friendlies .
I can 't get a shot .
Oh , man , this is FUBAR .
We got a group there at twelve o 'clock .
L 've got three on the ground .
Got four on the ground . Got four .
16 down .
I got two by the jeep .
Jesus !
I don 't see who 's a target .
On the move ! On the move ! On the move !
Move it right ! Move it right !
I can 't find another damn target here .
I can 't get a shot .
Whiskey Three , why have you stopped firing ?
Come in , Whiskey Three .
Abandon selective targeting .
Shoot everything . Targets are now free .
I cannot contain spreading .
We 've lost control .
All units , all units ,
this is Medical Commanding Officer Sierra Lima .
Please be on the lookout for a young boy , age 12 , name Andy .
If he is located , he must be immediately evacuated
from the containment zone .
We have to find Andy .
We have to find him !
It 's okay. lt 's okay . We 're gonna find him .
L 'm gonna find him , I promise .
L 'm gonna get him out of here .
L 'm gonna get you both out of here .
Trust me .
Which shot ?
Abandon selective targeting .
All targets are now free .
What ? Confirm order .
Rooftop units , target everyone at ground level .
No exceptions .
Repeat : no exceptions .
Run !
Three down ! One of ours down there !
Three o 'clock !
Taking ' em down , taking ' em down .
That 's it , at three o 'clock !
Kid ! Over here !
Take ' em out ! Take ' em out !
I got two fuckers on me . Doyle , I got two fuckers on me !
Fuck .
Fuck !
$ 4 '
Shh , shh , shh .
It 's all right. lt 's all right .
Tam ?
$ 4 '
This is madness .
What 's happening ?
They 're shooting everybody .
Why ?
It makes no sense .
It makes perfect sense .
It 's Code Red .
$ 4 '
I saw Dad .
Where ?
He 's one of them .
SCARLET ; Step one : kill the infected .
Step two : containment .
If containment fails ...
step three : extermination .
And now they won 't stop until everyone is dead .
So what do we do ?
I mean , I 'm not sitting around hereto get exterminated .
We 've got to get out of here .
If we take one step out of that door ,
if the infected don 't get us , the snipers will .
Well , you don 't have a choice , my friend .
Right now it 's dark out there .
The snipers can see through their night scopes , but ...
at least you have some limited cover from the infected .
But , you know , ifyou want to wait till sunup ,
then you 're as good as dead .
Who are you ?
Sergeant Doyle , Delta , Rooftop Unit .
Why aren 't you at your post ?
Why EVENT you ?
Look , you guys do what you want , but , uh ...
I 'm gonna get the fuck out of here .
You coming ?
' Kay , come on .
There 's less shooting .
Maybe they 've got it under control .
Or less shooters .
All right , listen , I need you guys
to look at me and only me , okay ?
You run when I run .
Be my shadow , that 's it , right ?
Get around back .
Watch her .
Ready ?
Let 's go .
Stay .
Doyle , come in .
Then go .
Doyle , where the fuck are you , man ?
Ground level ,
District One .
Shit ! Closed frequency .
Copy that .
What the fuck are you doing there ?
Listen to me , you 've got some serious shit coming your way .
We 've already got some serious shit .
No . I 'm not fucking playing ; this is worse .
The air cav , theyjust got their orders .
They 're firebombing
all of District One .
That was fast .
Outbreak is out of control . They 're taking no chances .
So unless you are out of the target zone ,
you are getting cooked , you got me ?
How long we got ?
They 're already on their way .
You got four minutes , tops .
But listen , I got some
clear landing ground at Regents Park .
That 's the pickup point . Got it ?
L 'll be back in touch .
Hey , Doyle , you fuckin ' better be .
All right , look , guys , we got to run , okay ?
Just stay low and stay fast .
Okay ? After me . Let 's go .
Sniper !
- Back ! Back ! Back ! - Get down ! Sniper !
Get back ! Get back !
- Back ! - Andy , get in !
lt 's okay .
It 'sjust a flesh wound .
All right .
Multiple shots , one hit .
He 's panicked , and no marksman .
All right .
- What 's your name ? - Sam .
Hey , Sam . Get close .
You see that doorway ?
I need you to run as fast as you can
in a zigzag like this , okay ?
And don 't stop for anything , okay ?
You want me to be bait .
No , no . Look , he 's gonna
take shots at you , all right ?
But he 's gonna miss .
All right ? He 's gonna expose his position .
It means I get a shot at him , and I won 't miss .
You 're out of your fucking mind .
- There 's no way I 'm going out there . - Stay back .
Two minutes , we 're all gonna die .
You want that ?
' No !
Fuck !
Good work , kid .
The fence ! Watch it , watch it !
Behind me .
Go ! Go !
Go !
Come on .
Come on , come on .
Jump !
This is Red Fox One pouring whiskey .
Keep going . We 'll be safe under the river .
$ 4 '
Go ! Go !
Come on ! Come on !
Run ! Run !
$ 4 '
Bring in bio-soldier units .
Fan out to the predesignated positions .
Bio units , copy .
Use of chemical weapons authorized .
Repeat : all units ,
chemical weapons are authorized .
$ 4 '
Stay close .
They left us again .
Do you think Mum 's still alive ?
Not this time .
You look a little pale .
Blood makes me nauseous .
You never answered my question .
About why you left your post .
I got that boy in my sights .
He 's not a target anymore .
When we were separated ...
I thought I 'd lost you , too .
We won 't get separated again .
We 'll stay together , whatever happens .
Whatever happens .
It 's all fucked .
You hear it all over the radios - fucked .
Anyway ... what about you ?
Why the hell are you here ?
Their mother ...
had very special blood .
Natural kind of immunity to the virus .
Not all genetic traits are passed on , you know .
They can skip a generation or vanish altogether , but ...
But they might have it .
It 's a possibility .
So their lives are far more valuable than mine .
Or yours .
I got it .
Doyle !
DOyle !
Flynn , go .
You made it .
I knew you 'd do it , buddy .
Listen , I am coming to you right now ,
but keep a lookout , okay ?
There 's confirmed sightings of infected
that have escaped the fire bombings .
Give me an ETA .
About 60 .
Minutes ?
No .
Seconds .
Kids , come on !
Get down .
Get down ! Get down .
$ 4 '
I see you !
Coming in !
Jesus , Doyle , you got people with you .
Who the fuck are those people ? !
DOyle !
I can 't take them !
We will get shot out of the sky if I try to land ...
No , no , don 't take them to base !
Take them over the channel !
What ? !
You got to get these kids out of here , Flynn !
Get the fuck in , Doyle ! I 'm not taking them !
- L 'm not leaving them ! - Get me out of here !
Hey ! Get him off of there !
Get the fuck off ... !
Okay .
- Stop ! - Come on !
Flynn , we 're gonna fucking
die down here ! Do something !
Come on , you fuckers .
Get up , get up , get up !
Run ! Move it !
Don 't look back !
Keep going !
Keep going .
Fuck you .
Doyle , come in !
Doyle ! You need to get to safe ground !
Get to the stadium !
Ditch those people !
L 'm not taking them .
Flynn , come in .
Flynn , goddamn it , I know you can hear me .
Fuck the Code Red . Fuck the chain of command .
L 'm stuck out here and need an extraction , goddamn it .
Better fucking be there , because we will be .
Hey , you okay ?
Yeah ?
Bet you 're tired , huh ?
Me , too .
Look , I need you to help me , okay ?
Help me with your sister .
You got that ?
Come on , got to go .
Got to go . Go , go , go , go , go !
$ 4 '
Gas ! Get back !
Get back ! Come on !
It 's gas !
- Get in the car ! - Run !
- Get in the car ! - Come on !
Get in the car ! Get in the car ! Hurry up !
Come on , come on , get in , get in !
Get in !
Go , go , go !
Get the vents ! Get the vents !
It won 't start !
We 're gonna be fine , all right ?
Just keep trying -
- Keep trying ! - It won 't start !
Come on . Come on ! Come on !
Keep trying ! Keep trying !
It won 't start !
- It won 't fucking start ! - Fuck me .
It won 't start .
Put your foot on the clutch .
All right , pop the clutch when I tell you , okay ?
You get them to the stadium .
Okay ?
Keep your head down .
I 'll meet you there .
DOyle !
POD it !
Go !
Go " !
Oh , my God !
Okay .
Scarlet !
They 're shooting at us !
Okay , let 's go !
Go on through here , guys .
just hold onto the rails .
Careful , guys .
Okay .
It 's okay . I can see . I can see .
Just keep going down .
Okay .
Keep walking straight , guys ,
holding against the wall .
You 're doing really well .
You 're doing great .
Okay , get back , get back !
Against the wall !
Okay , good .
Just stay close .
Slightly to the right , Andy .
It 's okay .
I know ... I can see . lt 's okay .
L 've got the night sight on .
You 're doing great . just hold , hold the rail .
Nice and slow down the stairs , okay ?
Stop , stop , stop !
Right now !
Okay , Tammy , to your left .
Good . Okay .
Good girl just straight ...
Now , nice and slow . Slower .
Stop ! Stop ! Stop , honey !
It 's okay ! lt 's okay !
It 's okay , all right ?
Grab ahold of the other railing , okay ?
Scarlet , I can 't see anything !
Okay , go to your right .
Go to your right .
All right , try and skip ...
just-just put your leg far out in front of you , okay ?
Good girl . Hold onto the rail .
Careful !
Andy ! Where are you ? !
Andy ! Where are you , Andy ? !
Answer me !
Where are you ? !
Tammy !
Scarlet !
Tammy , I 'm coming ! I 'm right here !
Scarlet , I 've lost Andy .
It 's okay. lt 's okay . I 'm right here .
L 've lost Andy .
It 's okay .
There you go .
Just slowly , towards me ...
I lost Andy .
We 'll find Andy .
Scarlet !
Andy !
Where are you ? !
Scarlet .
Tammy ?
Scarlet ? !
No !
Don 't !
We stay together ,
whatever happens .
No !
Andy !
Andy , no !
No , Andy !
Andy ! Andy !
No !
Andy !
$ 4 '
Tammy , am I one of them ?
No .
No , you 're not .
$ 4 '
Stop !
Where 's Doyle ?
It 's just us .
Come on .
Get in .
Come on !
$ 4 '
We need your help .